Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Domestic Advertisements, part 1, 1875-2001 and undated, bulk 1920s-1990s RL.00687
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Product Classification Index
  - Personal products
    - Apparel
      - Phoenix Hosiery (Small Files Series)
      - Real Silk (hosiery) (Small Files Series)
      - Saga Mink: see Mink International (Main Files Series)
      - Salvatore Ferragamo (Small Files Series)
      - Samsonite (luggage) (Main Files Series)
      - Sasson Jeans, Inc. (Small Files Series)
      - Webb Young (woolens) (Small Files Series)
      - Wool Bureau (Small Files Series)
    - Cameras and optical products
      - Bausch and Lomb (optical) (Main Files Series)
      - Eastman Kodak (camera and photography) (Main Files Series)
      - Eyelab (optical) (Small Files Series)
    - Cigarettes and tobacco products
      - Brown and Williamson (Small Files Series)
      - General Cigar (Small Files Series)
      - Liggett and Myers (Main Files Series)
      - Lorillard (Oversize only)
      - Philip Morris (Small Files Series)
      - R. J. Reynolds (Small Files Series)
    - Diet, health and fitness clubs
      - Bally Manufacturing Corporation (Main Files Series)
      - Chicago Health and Racquetball Club: see Bally Manufacturing (Main Files Series)
      - Health and Tennis Corp. of America: see Bally Manufacturing (Main Files Series)
      - Institute for Health Maintenance (Small Files Series)
      - Jenny Craig International Weight Loss Centers (Small Files Series)
      - Richard Simmons Anatomy Asylum: see Bally Manufacturing (Main Files Series)
      - Vic Tanny (Small Files Series)
    - Jewelry and watches
      - Aurea (jewelry) (Small Files Series)
      - DeBeers (diamonds) (Small Files Series)
      - Fred Joaillier (jewelry, watches) (Small Files Series)
      - Gruen Watch Makers Guild (Small Files Series)
      - Platinum Jewelry (Small Files Series)
      - Rolex (watches) (Main Files Series)
      - Seth Thomas (watches) (Small Files Series)
      - Webb Young Trader (jewelry) (Small Files Series)
    - Pet food and supplies
      - Coast Fishing Co. (Small Files Series)
      - Lowe's (Small Files Series)
    - Sporting goods
      - American Machine Foundry Co. (bowling) (Small Files Series)
      - Dunlop (golf) (Small Files Series)
      - Evans Products (bikes) (Small Files Series)
      - Hi-Tech Sports (Small Files Series)
      - Outboard Marine Corp. (Small Files Series)
      - PGA 61st Golf Championship (Small Files Series)
      - Prince (Small Files Series)
    - Toys and games
      - Activision (video games) (Small Files Series)
      - American Mechanical Toy Co. (Small Files Series)
      - Bandai (Small Files Series)
      - Fisher-Price (Small Files Series)
      - Jimsons Novelties and Gags (Small Files Series)
      - Original Appalachian Artworks (dolls) (Small Files Series)
      - Play Cable (Small Files Series)
      - Selchow and Righter (Small Files Series)
      - Toys 'R' Us (Small Files Series)
      - U.S. Playing Card Co. (Main Files Series)
  - Public service
    - Advertising Council (Main Files Series)
    - American Cancer Society (Main Files Series)
    - American Foundation for AIDS Research (Main Files Series)
    - American Library Association (Oversize only)
    - American Red Cross (Main Files Series)
    - Archdiocese of Detroit (Small Files Series)
    - Better Schools (Main Files Series)
    - Bob Hope Heart Research Institute (Main Files Series)
    - BOM (Boysville) (Main Files Series)
    - Boy Scouts of America (Main Files Series)
    - Boys' Club of America (Oversize only)
    - California Arts Council (Small Files Series)
    - California Film Commission (Small Files Series)
    - California Tourism (Small Files Series)
    - Catholic Charities Department of Foster Family Service (Main Files Series)
    - Children's Literacy Initiative (Main Files Series)
    - Children's Memorial Hospital (Main Files Series)
    - Church World Service (Main Files Series)
    - Civil Defense (Main Files Series)
    - Coalition on Donation (Main Files Series)
    - Committee for Handgun Control (Main Files Series)
    - COPSA Institute for Alzheimer's Disease (Main Files Series)
    - Crusade for Freedom (Main Files Series)
    - Cystic Fibrosis Foundation (Main Files Series)
    - Executive Service Corp. of Chicago (Main Files Series)
    - Henry Street Settlement (Oversize only)
    - Hospice Foundation of Southeastern Michigan (Main Files Series)
    - Literary Council of Chicago (Main Files Series)
    - March of Dimes (Main Files Series)
    - National Bible Week (Main Files Series)
    - New England Earth Day (Main Files Series)
    - New York Cares (Main Files Series)
    - Nixon-Lodge campaign (Oversize only)
    - Nurse Recruitment (Main Files Series)
    - Partnership for a Drug Free America (Main Files Series)
    - President's Council on Youth Opportunity (Main Files Series)
    - Providence-St. Mel High School (Main Files Series)
    - Red Nose Day USA for Sudden Infant Death Syndrome (SIDS) (Main Files Series)
    - Religion in American Life (Main Files Series)
    - Salvation Army of Greater New York (Main Files Series)
    - San Francisco AIDS Foundation (Main Files Series)
    - Save the Cable Cars (Main Files Series)
    - Statue of Liberty-Ellis Island Foundation (Main Files Series)
    - Survival Anglia Ltd. (Small Files Series)
    - United America (Main Files Series)
    - United Cerebral Palsy (Main Files Series)
    - United Foundations (Main Files Series)
    - United Way (Main Files Series)
    - Western States Advertising Partnership (Small Files Series)
  - Toiletries and cosmetics (beauty and hygiene)
    - Alberto-Culver (Main Files Series)
    - Andrew Jergens Co. (Main Files Series)
    - Bio Rics (Small Files Series)
    - Bristol Myers Squibb (Small Files Series)
    - Cheseborough-Pond's (Main Files Series)
    - Clairol (Small Files Series)
    - Clear Start (Small Files Series)
    - Condomania (Small Files Series)
    - Gillette (Main Files Series)
    - Guerlain, Inc. (Small Files Series)
    - J. B. Williams (Main Files Series)
    - Jovan (Main Files Series)
    - Lever Brothers (Main Files Series)
    - Mennen Company (Small Files Series)
    - Northam Warren (Odorono) (Small Files Series)
    - Pharma-Craft Corp. (Small Files Series)
    - Pro-Phy-Lac-Tic Brush Co. (Small Files Series)
    - S. C. Johnson and Son (Main Files Series)
    - Scott Paper Co. (Main Files Series)
    - Squibb: see Bristol Myers Squib (Small Files Series)
    - Teledyne Water Pik (Small Files Series)
    - Warner Lambert (Main Files Series)
  - Travel and transportation
    - Air travel
      - Allegheny Airlines: see U.S. Air
      - Hawaii Express (Small Files Series)
      - Helio Aircraft Corp. (Small Files Series)
      - McDonnell Douglas Corp. (Main Files Series)
      - Mexicana Airlines (Main Files Series)
      - National Airlines (Small Files Series)
      - Northeast Airline (Main Files Series)
      - Northwest Airlines (Small Files Series)
      - Pan-American World Airways (Main Files Series)
      - U.S. Air (Main Files Series)
    - Automotive
      - Automotive services
        - Car Care Council (Small Files Series)
        - Diners/Fugazy (limo service) (Small Files Series)
        - National Car Rental (Small Files Series)
        - National Institute for Automotive Services Excellence (Small Files Series)
        - Precision Tune (Small Files Series)
        - Vehicle Emissions Check Committee (Main Files Series)
      - Gas and oil
        - Amerada Hess (Small Files Series)
        - Chevron (Small Files Series)
        - Mobile Oil (Small Files Series)
        - Phillips Petroleum Co. (Main Files Series)
        - Shell (Main Files Series)
        - Signal (Small Files Series)
        - STP (Small Files Series)
      - Manufacturers
        - Continental Motors (Small Files Series)
        - Ford (Main Files Series)
        - General Motors (Small Files Series)
        - Kawasaki Motor Co. (motorcycles) (Main Files Series)
        - Thomas B. Jeffery and Co. (Rambler tour car) (Small Files Series)
      - Parts
        - A.P.S. Auto Parts (Small Files Series)
        - ANCO (Anderson Co.) (Small Files Series)
        - Car X (Small Files Series)
        - Champion Spark Plugs (Main Files Series)
        - Colt Industries (Small Files Series)
        - Corning Glass (Small Files Series)
        - Evans Products (Small Files Series)
        - Ford (Main Files Series)
        - Fram Corp. (Small Files Series)
        - General Motors (Small Files Series)
        - Industrial Alcohol Institute (Small Files Series)
        - Loctite (Small Files Series)
        - Midas (mufflers) (Small Files Series)
        - Monroe Auto Equipment: see Tenneco (Main Files Series)
        - NAPA Mufflers and Shocks: see Tenneco (Main Files Series)
        - Purolator (Main Files Series)
        - Robert Bosch Corp. (Small Files Series)
        - Safe Brands (antifreeze) (Small Files Series)
        - Tenneco (Main Files Series)
        - Walker Manufacturing Co.: see Tenneco (Main Files Series)
      - Tires
        - Firestone (Small Files Series)
        - Goodyear (Main Files Series)
    - Cruises
      - American Cruises (Small Files Series)
      - Circle Line (Small Files Series)
      - Farrell Steamship Lines (Small Files Series)
      - Premier Cruise Lines (Main Files Series)
      - Princess Cruises (Small Files Series)
      - U. S. Lines (Main Files Series)
    - Hotels and resorts
      - Big Sky of Montana, Inc. (Small Files Series)
      - Harrison Centers (Small Files Series)
      - Hilton International (Small Files Series)
      - Holiday Inn (Small Files Series)
      - Hyatt Hotels Corp. (Main Files Series)
      - Intercontinental Hotels (Main Files Series)
      - MPAC Sports Day (Small Files Series)
      - Town House (Small Files Series)
    - Railroads
      - Chicago, Milwaukee, St. Paul and Pacific Railroad (Main Files Series)
      - Conductron Corp. (Small Files Series)
      - Grand Central (Small Files Series)
      - Milwaukee Road Raliroad (Small Files Series)
      - New York Central System (Small Files Series)
      - Norfolk Southern Corp. (Small Files Series)
      - Northern Pacific Railroad (Small Files Series)
      - Pennsylvania Railroad (Small Files Series)
    - Tourism
      - California Tourism (Small Files Series)
      - Georgia Department of Tourism (Small Files Series)
      - Turkish Tourism (Small Files Series)